

# Christopher Nohall, Software Developer

christopher.nohall@gmail.com

## DETAILS

+86 176 8553 7870

### LINKS

www.nohall.nu www.begtool.se

#### SKILLS

Pedagogical

Complex Problem
Solving

Interpreting

### LANGUAGES

English

Swedish

Chinese

Korean

### **PROFILE**

Dedicated programmer with several years of experience effectively working on completing the tasks and projects at hand. Bringing forth a lifelong passion for solving problems, combined wit a curiosity to learn new concepts. Adept in building positive relationships with workmates and clients. I am committed to bringing my best to each project.

### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

### Software Developer, Nohall Solutions

Oct 2016 — Present, Jeju-Si, Republic of Korea

One of my latest projects was building begtool.se from scratch.

Begtool.se is a Swedish website for people who want to sell their second-hand tools. I built the website using the MERN-stack. The costumer was very keen on making the website responsive. They target the mobile market and want to make it easy for people to put ads from their phones. Feel free to check it out!

### English Teacher, a Chinese Middle-School

Jul 2015 — Jun 2016, Qingdao, China

### EDUCATION

### Royal Institute of Technology

Sep 2009 - Jun 2010, Stockholm, Sweden

Studied Maths, Physics and Engineering

### Dalarnas Högskola

Sep 2013 - Jun 2015

Studied Chinese Linguistics, Business and Culture

### REFERENCES

References available upon request